<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>
	<XmlExtensions.SettingsMenuDef>
		<defName>NotSettings_Info_AboutAllGirls_WVC</defName>
		<modId>honkai.girls.sergkart</modId>
		<settings>
			<li Class="XmlExtensions.Setting.Text">
				<text>About girls:\n\n&lt;color=#a2c8ff&gt;Valkyries - These girls are the humanoid version. They can do everything normal pawns can do. Have psi abilities, build, craft, get royal titles, etc. That is, to be full-fledged pawns. Valkyries have several subspecies. The settings of the Valkyries and their subspecies are located in the "Humanlikes" tab.&lt;/color&gt;\n\n&lt;color=#ffcea2&gt;Royal Dryads (Dryad Girls) - are dryads that have a girl skin, they are basically more effective than ordinary dryads, but do not completely replace them. Their settings are in "Valkyries" tab, and their humanoid version is in the "Humanlikes" tab.&lt;/color&gt;\n\n&lt;color=#f5ffa2&gt;Mother of the Dryads - a subspecies of the Valkyries and therefore inherits most of the settings and parameters from them. They have the abilities of the Gauranlen tree. Mother settings can be found in the "Humanlikes" tab.&lt;/color&gt;\n\n&lt;color=#cca2ff&gt;Herrschers - a subspecies of the Valkyries, they inherit most of the settings with the exception of appearance. But they are vastly superior to the Valkyries and are a combination of the Mothers' strength and the Valkyries' speed. The settings can be found in the "Humanlikes" tab.&lt;/color&gt;\n\n&lt;color=#a2adff&gt;ELF - a subspecies of the Valkyries. They are weak in combat and significantly inferior in strength to the Valkyries, however, they are better at tending wounds and better at any job. They have unique skins.&lt;/color&gt;\n\nInfo:\n- Appearance settings for Royal Dryads are located here, for Valkyries skins are selected in the "Humanlikes" tab.\n- Incoming damage settings are common for all girls, by default all girls receive full damage (1.0). Just below you can change the overall multiplier.\n\n&lt;color=#FFE66F&gt;- Thanks to rot03065  for permission to use the girls from IG! This allows Valkyries to have the appearance of Insect Girls.&lt;/color&gt;&lt;color=#64b8ff&gt;\n- Thanks to Psyche for permission to use the girls from the "kemomimihouse" mod!&lt;/color&gt;&lt;color=#c8c8ff&gt;\n- Thanks to 死萌 for permission to use the Mimikko girls!&lt;/color&gt;</text>
				<tKey>HGS_General_GeneralTab_MainInfoAboutGirls_WVC</tKey>
			</li>
		</settings>
	</XmlExtensions.SettingsMenuDef>
</Defs>
